In the last lecture I created a basic react application which you either now downloaded or where you
Son derste, imdi indirdiiniz ya da takip ettiiniz temel
followed along,
bir tepki
now it's time to install some dependencies,
uygulamas oluturdum, imdi
for example the react application obviously uses react or react-dom and the react router
bamllk kurma zaman geldi, rnein tepki uygulamas aka tepki veya tepki-dom ve tepki
so we should install all these production dependencies,
veren ynlendirici kullanyor, bu yzden
we do this with npm installed --save, not --save-dev because we want to indicate that
hepsini yklemeliyiz Bu retim bamllklar, bunu npm ile ykledik --save,
these are production dependencies and then it's react react-dom and react-router-dom, like this.
--save-dev deil, nk bunlarn retim bamllklar olduunu ve bunun gibi tepki-tepki ve tepki-ynlendirici-dom olduunu belirtmek istiyoruz.
These three dependencies are all separated with white spaces and are now installed and therefore
Bu  bamlln hepsi beyaz boluklarla ayrlm ve imdi
placed into the node module folder, appropriate entries with the latest versions are also added to the
kurulduktan sonra dm modl klasrne yerletirilmi, en son srmlere uygun giriler
package.json file as you can see.
de pakete eklenmitir. Grdnz gibi json dosyas.
With that we installed react,
Tepki kurduk, web paketini
we did install webpack a while ago already,
bir sre nce kurduk, imdi bir i
we now need to install a couple of other dependencies to build a workflow and I will add them step by
ak oluturmak iin bir ka tane baka bamllk kurmamz gerekiyor ve onlara ihtiya duyduumuzda
step whenever we need them.
bunlar adm adm ekleyeceiz.
So what I want to do is I now want to start with setting up the webpack configuration such that it is
Yani yapmak istediim ey imdi, yeni nesil javascript, css, resimler ve tm bu elenceli
able to handle next generation javascript,
eyleri ele alabilmesi iin
css, images and all that fun stuff.
web paketi yaplandrmasn kurmakla balamak istiyorum.
Let's start with this in the next lecture.
Bir sonraki derste bununla balayalm.